YURI BEKMETOV

QA Engineer

+7 (962) 752-88-69 bekmetov.ru



SUMMARY

Results-oriented engineer with 5+ years of experience in the QHSE field (Oil & Gas, construction industry). I'm looking for new opportunities to apply a structural approach and analytical skills in an IT field. Interested in frontend and mobile development.

EXPERIENCE

Chief QHSE Specialist / ISM Quality Curator

JSC ASE – ROSATOM (Egypt)

Nov 2020 - Nov 2022

- Development of procedures/plans and implementation on the project as a part of Integrated Management System (IMS).
- Communication with customer/contractors on safety related issues, collaboration with Quality, Lab, Survey departments.
- Participation in inspections, audits, verification of compliance license for construction, investigation of accidents, accounting and reporting.

HSE Specialist

Schlumberger (Russia & Central Asia)

Aug 2019 - Oct 2020

- Daily monitoring of the activities of the segments for the safe performance of work, preparation reports (Risk identification and Observation).
- Developing, updating and implementation of HARC (Hazard Analysis and Risk Control).
- Carrying out inspections, identifying hazards, checking compliance.

Fire safety engineer

Gazprom Oil & Gas – Russia

Sep 2014 - Nov 2018

- Daily monitoring of facilities for safe condition, equipment performance.
- Calculation of fire load, fire extinguishing equipment required.
- Carrying out control checks, preparation of acts of non-compliance.

SKILLS

GIT	Jira	SQL	Postman
НТТР	REST	Fiddler	HTML
CSS	IS	XCode	MacOS

EDUCATION

Astrakhan Institute of Engineering and Construction Engineer's degree

Fire prevention and Safety Technology/Technician – 2009 – 2014

Udemy

Software Testing 2022

QUALIFICATION

ISO 45001:2018

Lead Auditor Training Course OH&S Management System

Siberian Training Center

Schlumberger Facilitator / Trainer

LANGUAGES

Russian	•••••	
Native English B2-C1	••••	
Arabic	••••	

ABOUT

Married, no children. Hobbies: chess, guitar, table tennis. ISTJ, positive thinker.